<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Shawn McDaniel</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Shawn McDaniel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:35:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Domain Squatting, BEC, Fake Invoices...oh my</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/posttwo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:35:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/posttwo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;About a year ago I had a friend call me with a minor concern. They worked for a
reputable general contractor that worked with some very high-end clients.
Incredibly wealthy is what that means. They were wondering how an email could
appear to have come from one of the managers of the company requesting payment
from a client. This piqued my interest. Honestly I had a hard time wrapping my
head around the circumstances, as the timeline was not explained well. I will
attempt to do a better job explaining it below:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Wall Street to Main Street</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/postone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:35:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/postone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used to build houses. I was pretty good at it, believe it or not. My formative
years in the military were squeezed in between years of building, managing and
struggling in the construction industry. It&amp;rsquo;s a hard life, but the pay can be
great and there is something to be said about building a physical thing that
will be around for a long time. Craftsmanship is a unique trait, and the trades
are where some of the most amazing things get built. Perhaps it may be common
knowledge that the trades are notoriously averse to the tides of technology,
perhaps not. I would argue that for being such a large sector of small
businesses, there is a problem with the adoption of technology. According to the
Small Business Administration, greater that 10% of all small to medium sized
businesses are in the construction sector. Even more astounding is that about
99.9% of all construction companies are considered small to medium sized
businesses. So, being conservative with our math, if about 45% of SMBs make up
the GDP of the United States, we can assume about 4-5% of GDP comes from this
uniquely small construction sector. This is not trivial.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
